A Guide to the ODU Poster Collection, 1974-1990
Special Collections and University Archives, Patricia W. and J. Douglas Perry Library, Old Dominion University
Special Collections and University Archives, Patricia W. and J. Douglas Perry Library, Old Dominion University
ODU Poster Collection 1974-1990
Special Collections and University Archives, Patricia W. and J. Douglas Perry Library, Old Dominion University
30
7 oversized boxes
Old Dominion University
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Open to researchers without restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Unknown.
Historical Information
The ODU Poster Collection contains a wide range of posters of musical performances, plays, athletic events, academic programs, student activities, lectures, discussions, seminars, readings, and festivals. They document recruitment foci, program offerings and the academic, political and cultural environment of the university.
Scope and Content
The collection contains approximately 450 oversized color posters, dated from 1974 to 1990. Many of the posters are undated. The collection is arranged into the following series: I Administration and Services, II Academic Programs, III Departmental Events, IV ODU Organizations, V University Sponsored Community Events, VI Athletics.
Arrangement
Posters are arranged into alphabetically within each category.
Index Terms
Old Dominion University; Posters--Virginia--Norfolk--20th century; Posters
Contents List
- Administration and Services 1977-1979, 1985-1988
  Contains of posters advertising services or policies on Admissions, Career advising, Financial Aid, Honor Council, Housing, Public Safety, Womens Center and Miscellaneous.
  - Admissions 1978-1979, 1985
    - A Historical, Recreational, & Educational Experience 1978 (Box-folder 1:1)
    - Class Registration 1979 (Box-folder 1:2)
    - Graduate and Professional School Day (Box-folder 1:3)
    - The Military and Tuition Rates at ODU 1985 (Box-folder 1:4)
    - Mind Power at ODU, Recruitment 1978 (Box-folder 1:5)
    - ODU Enrollment/Admissions (Box-folder 1:6)
    - ODU is Going Your Way, Recruitment (Box-folder 1:7)
    - Senior Scholars (Box-folder 1:8)
    - Transfer Day 1978 (Box-folder 1:9)
    - Transfer Day Fall Term 1978 (Box-folder 1:10)
  - Career/Job Oriented 1977, 1986
    - Assistance Referral Center (Box-folder 1:11)
    - Career Development Services (Box-folder 1:12)
    - Career Exploration Symposiums 1977 (Box-folder 1:13)
    - Co-op Education 1986 (Box-folder 1:14)
    - Fast, Fast Relief from Those Job Hunting Headaches (Box-folder 1:15)
    - Looking for a Job or a Career? Educational Opportunity Center (Box-folder 1:16)
  - Financial Aid
    - Financial Aid (Box-folder 1:17)
    - Financial Aid Wizardry (Box-folder 1:18)
  - Honor Council
    - Academic Dishonesty Thrives on Weakness (Box-folder 1:19)
    - An Honorable Institution (Box-folder 1:20)
    - Cheating Counts Against You (Box-folder 1:21)
    - Consider an Investment in Us! University Annual Fund (Box-folder 1:22)
    - Honor Council (Box-folder 1:23)
    - Let's Keep ODU Honorable (Box-folder 1:24)
    - ODU Honor Pledge (Box-folder 1:25)
    - ODU Honor System (Box-folder 1:26)
    - Your Paper Should Match Your Mind (Box-folder 1:27)
  - Housing
    - Housing for Rent, ODU Housing (Box-folder 1:28)
    - Welcome to Powhatan II (Box-folder 1:29)
  - Miscellaneous 1987-1988
    - Carpool to Class (Box-folder 1:30)
    - Feelin Great in 88: Explore the Dimensions of Wellness, ODU Student Health Center 1988 (Box-folder 1:31)
    - FOCUS- Finding Options & Choices in Using Substances, Alcohol Education Committee 1987 (Box-folder 1:32)
    - Old Dominion University (Box-folder 1:33)
    - Please Hear What Im Not Saying, Poem in Calligraphy (Box-folder 1:34)
    - Statement of Work Values, ODU 1988 (Box-folder 1:35)
    - The Classroom Hotline, Work Management Center (Box-folder 1:36)
    - The Taped Information Line, Campus Information Center (Box-folder 1:37)
    - Dental Hygiene Clinic (Box-folder 1:38)
    - Writing Center (Box-folder 1:39)
  - Public Safety
    - ODU Escort Service, Department of Public Safety (Box-folder 1:40)
    - ODU Police Note: Theft Protection (Box-folder 1:41)
  - Womens Center 1988
    - Now You Can Blow the Whistle, Students Organized for Safety & Student Affairs, Residence Life, Womens Center (Box-folder 1:42)
    - Womens Center Brown Bag Lunch Series (Box-folder 1:43)
    - Every Womens Festival, Womens Center (Box-folder 1:44)
    - Lunchtime Discussion Series, Womens Center (Box-folder 1:45)
    - Sexual Harassment, Womens Center 1988 (Box-folder 1:46)
- Academic Programs 1977-1990
  Primarily contains recruiting posters for different degree programs.
  - Allied Health Careers Opportunity Program (Box-folder 2:1)
  - Art (Box-folder 2:2)
  - Atmospheric & Earth Sciences (Box-folder 2:3)
  - Biological Sciences 1977-1986 (Box-folder 2:4)
  - Business 1983 (Box-folder 2:5)
  - Center for Personal and Professional Development (Box-folder 2:6)
  - Chemistry 1980 (Box-folder 2:7)
  - Communication: Mini Courses 1985-1986 (Box-folder 2:8)
  - Dental Hygiene (Box-folder 2:9)
  - Allied Health Careers Opportunity Program (Box-folder 2:10)
  - Economics 1979 (Box-folder 2:12)
  - Engineering 1978-1988 (Box-folder 2:13)
  - English 1979-1988 (Box-folder 2:14)
  - Geological Sciences 1983 (Box-folder 2:15)
  - History 1978 (Box-folder 2:16)
  - Humanities 1979 (Box-folder 2:17)
  - Industrial Arts (Box-folder 2:18)
  - International Studies 1978 (Box-folder 2:19)
  - Liberal Arts (Box-folder 2:20)
  - Mathematical Sciences (Box-folder 2:21)
  - Oceanography 1979-1990 (Box-folder 2:22)
  - Physics 1978 (Box-folder 2:23)
  - Political Science and Geography (Box-folder 2:24)
  - Psychology 1978 (Box-folder 2:25)
  - School of Sciences & Health 1979-1980 (Box-folder 2:26)
  - Sociology (Box-folder 2:27)
  - Structural Acoutics and Fatigue (Box-folder 2:28)
  - Summer & Fall Topics in the School of Arts & Letters (Box-folder 2:29)
  - Undergraduate Degree Programs 1988 (Box-folder 2:30)
  - Urban Studies 1978-1979 (Box-folder 2:31)
  - Women in Science (Box-folder 2:32)
  - Womens Re-entry, Returning to School (Box-folder 2:33)
  - Arts & Letters 1979 (Box-folder 3:1)
  - Courses Offered 1978-1979 (Box-folder 3:2)
  - Education (Box-folder 3:3)
  - Engineering (Box-folder 3:4)
  - Foreign Travel/Study Abroad 1979 (Box-folder 3:5)
  - General Douglas Fellowship (Box-folder 3:6)
  - History 1977-1980 (Box-folder 3:7)
  - Humanities 1982-1983 (Box-folder 3:8)
  - Industrial Arts (Box-folder 3:9)
  - Liberal Arts 1978, 1985 (Box-folder 3:10)
  - Oceanography 1986 (Box-folder 3:11)
  - Off Campus Degrees (Box-folder 3:12)
  - Program for Afloat College Education PACE (Box-folder 3:13)
  - Seaport System Management 1978 (Box-folder 3:14)
  - Summer School Posters (Box-folder 3:15)
  - Womens Studies Series 1979-1981 (Box-folder 3:16)
- Schools/Departments 1974-1975, 1977-1983, 1985-1989
  Contains posters for events sponsored by the departments or schools of Arts & Letters, Engineering, English, School of Sciences and Health, History, Institute of Scottish Studies, Interdisciplinary Studies, International Programs, International Relations, Music, Nursing and Womens Studies.
  - Arts & Letters 1979-1982, 1985-1986, 1988
    - Ascent of Man Film Series (Box-folder 4:1)
    - Economic Education Forum: Consumer Protection, Center for Economic Education (Box-folder 4:2)
    - Elise N. Hofheimer Art Library (Box-folder 4:3)
    - Ethics and the Police, Institute of Applied Ethics/Dept. of Sociology & CRJS/ Dept. of Philosophy 1982 (Box-folder 4:4)
    - Japanese Classical Music, Institute of Asian Studies 1988 (Box-folder 4:5)
    - Justice as Legislatures? The Supreme Court Today, Political Science (Box-folder 4:6)
    - Multicultural Center -- Noel Pointer (Box-folder 4:7)
    - Multicultural Summer Theatre -- Babes on Broadway (Box-folder 4:8)
    - Technology: Its Effects on the Workplace, College of Education 1988 (Box-folder 4:9)
    - The Folktale: Bearer of Art, Tradition & Morality, Dept. of Speech Communication & Theatre Arts 1986 (Box-folder 4:10)
    - Town Meeting on Foreign Trade & Economic Sanctions, Center for Economic Education 1980 (Box-folder 4:11)
    - Town Meeting on Inflation 1979 (Box-folder 4:12)
    - Town Meetings 1985 (Box-folder 4:13)
    - Who Speaks for the Child: The Question of Proxy Consent, Dept. of Philosophy 1981 (Box-folder 4:14)
  - Art 1979
    - UFO (Underground Film Organization) Movie Poster (Box-folder 4:15)
    - UFO (Underground Film Organization) My Night at Mauds 1979 (Box-folder 4:16)
    - UFO Movies Poster -- Event Schedule (Box-folder 4:17)
    - Fay Zetlin (Box-folder 4:18)
  - Engineering 1979, 1981
    - Does Concrete Float? Mid Atlantic Concrete Canoe Race 1979 (Box-folder 4:19)
    - Does Concrete Float? Student Chapter American Society of Civil Engineers 1981 (Box-folder 4:20)
  - English 1978-1979, 1980-1983, 1988
    - 1st Annual ODU Arts Reunion 1978 (Box-folder 4:21)
    - AWP Award Series-Competition (Box-folder 4:22)
    - Cornelius Eady: A Reading (Box-folder 4:23)
    - Edward Hirsch: A Reading 1981 (Box-folder 4:24)
    - Elizabeth Cox: A Reading 1983 (Box-folder 4:25)
    - Great Scenes from Shakespeare 1979 (Box-folder 4:26)
    - Great Scenes from Shakespeare 1980 (Box-folder 4:27)
    - June Jordan: A Reading 1980 (Box-folder 4:28)
    - Literary Festival, 2nd Annual 1979 (Box-folder 4:29)
    - Literary Festival, Kenkesey in Person, 5th Annual 1982 (Box-folder 4:30)
    - My Friend Bill Faulkner (Box-folder 4:31)
    - Shakespeares World of Love 1983 (Box-folder 4:32)
    - Sharon Olds: A Reading, Visiting Writers Program 1983 (Box-folder 4:33)
    - Siv Cedering: A Reading, Visiting Writers Series 1983 (Box-folder 4:34)
    - Visiting Writers Series: Debra Bruce 1988 (Box-folder 4:35)
    - Visiting Writers Series: Lee Zacharias: A Reading 1981 (Box-folder 4:36)
    - Visiting Writers Series: Susanna Kaysen 1988 (Box-folder 4:37)
  - School of Sciences and Health Professions 1978, 1985
    - Energy in the Future: A Geological View 1978 (Box-folder 4:38)
    - Health A Personal Responsibility (Box-folder 4:39)
    - Meteorology of Mars 1978 (Box-folder 4:40)
    - Science & Society 1978 (Box-folder 4:41)
    - The Interdisciplinary Conference on the Sexual Victimization of Children, Office of Continuing Education 1985 (Box-folder 4:42)
  - History 1974-1975
    - Palmerston The Immoral One (Box-folder 4:43)
    - An Evening with Senator Byrd, Phi Alpha Theta 1975 (Box-folder 4:44)
    - Cyprus in Historical Perspective 1974 (Box-folder 4:45)
    - Days that Tried Mens Souls, History Club and Phi Alpha Theta (Box-folder 4:46)
    - Election Review, Phi Alpha Theta 1974 (Box-folder 4:47)
    - First Semester: History Club and Phi Alpha Theta (Box-folder 4:48)
    - ODU: A Golden Jubilee Montage (Box-folder 4:49)
    - Old Dominion University: A Half Century of Service by Dr. Sweeney (Box-folder 4:50)
    - The How and Why of Norfolk Gardens, Phi Alpha Theta & League of Womens Voters 1974 (Box-folder 4:51)
    - USA Crisis of Allegiance, History Club and Phi Alpha Theta (Box-folder 4:52)
    - Virginia Politics: Past and Present (Box-folder 4:53)
  - Institute of Scottish Studies 1977-1979, 1983, 1988
    - 7th Annual Conference on Scottish Studies 1978 (Box-folder 4:54)
    - 8th Annual Conference on Scottish Studies 1979 (Box-folder 4:55)
    - 10th Annual Conference on Scottish Studies, Institute of Scottish Studies (Box-folder 4:56)
    - 12th Annual Conference on Scottish Studies 1983 (Box-folder 4:57)
    - Jean Redpath in Concert 1977 (Box-folder 4:58)
    - The Social World of Scottish Enlightenment 1988 (Box-folder 4:59)
    - The Society of Patrons & Friends of, The Ballads of Scotland 1978 (Box-folder 4:60)
    - Till all the Seas Run Dry (Box-folder 4:61)
  - Interdisciplinary Studies 1977-1979
    - Anticipatory Democracy: People in the Politics of the Future 1979 (Box-folder 4:62)
    - China and the Third World (Box-folder 4:63)
    - Chinese Communities under Mao 1979 (Box-folder 4:64)
    - Dr. Norman Bethune (Box-folder 4:65)
    - Educational Reform in the Peoples Republic of China (Box-folder 4:66)
    - Family Incorporation: Reclaiming an Endangered Institution (Box-folder 4:67)
    - Farming the Sea: A Solution to World Hunger (Box-folder 4:68)
    - Faustian Man Retrospect & Prospect 1977 (Box-folder 4:69)
    - Film Poster (Box-folder 4:70)
    - Films for the Future (Box-folder 4:71)
    - Future Shock (Box-folder 4:72)
    - Science and Public Policy (Box-folder 4:73)
    - Two Kinds of Soviet Youth: The Komosomol Boy Scout & The Underground Hippie, Visiting Scholars, Interdisciplinary Studies and Foreign Languages (Box-folder 4:74)
    - West Africa: The Ecological impact of Modernization 1978 (Box-folder 4:75)
    - Women in the 3rd World Partners in Modernization 1978 (Box-folder 4:76)
  - International Programs 1978-1983, 1985
    - 1st Annual International Film Festival, International Jubilee 1978 (Box-folder 4:77)
    - 2nd Annual International Jubilee 1979 (Box-folder 4:78)
    - 3rd Annual International Jubilee 1980 (Box-folder 4:79)
    - 4th Annual International Jubilee 1981 (Box-folder 4:80)
    - 5th Annual International Jubilee 1982 (Box-folder 4:81)
    - 6th Annual International Jubilee, Multicultural Center & Center for International Programs 1983 (Box-folder 4:82)
    - 8th Annual International Jubilee 1985 (Box-folder 4:83)
    - Ambassador Han Xu: For Stronger Ties China-US Relations, Institute of Asian Studies (Box-folder 4:84)
    - Films from the Middle East 1982 (Box-folder 4:85)
    - Japanese Literature through Film 1981 (Box-folder 4:86)
  - International Relations 1987-1989
    - Waldo Family Lecture Series on International Relations, George McGovern 1987 (Box-folder 4:87)
    - Waldo Family Lecture Series on International Relations, John B. Anderson 1988 (Box-folder 4:88)
    - Waldo Family Lecture Series on International Relations, Seymour M. Hersh 1989 (Box-folder 4:89)
  - Music
    - 3rd Annual Summer Brass Workshop (Box-folder 4:90)
    - 4th Annual Summer Brass Workshop (Box-folder 4:91)
    - 5th Annual Summer Brass Workshop (Box-folder 4:92)
    - 6th Annual Summer Brass Workshop (Box-folder 4:93)
    - 7th Annual Summer Brass Workshop (Box-folder 4:94)
    - Concert Choir, 2 posters (Box-folder 4:95)
    - Fall Concert, 2 posters (Box-folder 4:96)
    - Grainne Yeats: The Harp in History- Lecture Recital, 2 posters (Box-folder 4:97)
    - Marching Band Classic, 2 posters (Box-folder 4:98)
    - Old English Madrigal Christmas Dinner, 2 posters (Box-folder 4:99)
    - University Faculty Recital Series -- Benjamin Van Wye, 2 posters (Box-folder 4:100)
    - Wind Ensemble Spring Concert, 2 posters (Box-folder 4:101)
  - Nursing 1978-1980
    - 1st Annual Perkins Nursing Lectureship, The Nurses Role in Meeting Primary Care Needs 1977 (Box-folder 4:102)
    - 2nd Annual Perkins Nursing Lectureship, The Consumer: Health Care Deliver & the Profession of Nursing 1978 (Box-folder 4:103)
    - 3rd Annual Perkins Nursing Lectureship, A Forecast of Clinical Nursing Practice 1979 (Box-folder 4:104)
    - 4th Annual Perkins Nursing Lectureship 1980 (Box-folder 4:105)
  - Womens Studies 1987
    - Guerilla Girls (Box-folder 4:106)
    - Womens Studies 10th Anniversary Celebration: Bella Abzug 1987 (Box-folder 4:107)
    - Womens Studies Series 1987, 4 posters (Box-folder 4:108)
- ODU Organizations 1977-1984, 1986-1988
  Contains posters for the Activities Programming Board, ODU Ballet, ODU Players, Riverview Playhouse, University Gallery and other Student and Alumni organizations.
  - Activities Programming Board (APB) 1977-1984, 1987
    - 1st Annual Dinner-Dance 1978 (Box-folder 5:1)
    - 50 Hour Student Celebration (Box-folder 5:2)
    - Amazing Kreskin 1978 (Box-folder 5:3)
    - An Evening with John Anderson 1984 (Box-folder 5:4)
    - Angela Bofill (Box-folder 5:5)
    - APB Calendar April 197-? or 198-? (Box-folder 5:6)
    - APB Calendar April 1980 (Box-folder 5:7)
    - APB Calendar February 1982 (Box-folder 5:8)
    - APB Calendar March 1983 (Box-folder 5:9)
    - APB Calendar November 197-? or 198-? (Box-folder 5:10)
    - APB Calendar November 1981 (Box-folder 5:11)
    - APB Calendar October 197-? or 198-? (Box-folder 5:12)
    - APB Calendar September 1981 (Box-folder 5:13)
    - APB Dance with Brice Street (Box-folder 5:14)
    - Are you Normal? Should Dope be Legal? (Box-folder 5:15)
    - Big Blue Day featuring Staircase (Box-folder 5:16)
    - Black History Week (Box-folder 5:17)
    - Bob Zentz Traditional and Contemporary Songs and Tunes (Box-folder 5:18)
    - Christmas Dinner-Dance 1978 (Box-folder 5:19)
    - Comedy Film Festival (Box-folder 5:20)
    - Dance with Royal Kings (Box-folder 5:21)
    - David Frye & Choice (Box-folder 5:22)
    - Dixie Dregs (Box-folder 5:23)
    - DNA: Who Should Play God? 1978 (Box-folder 5:24)
    - Eric Pappas in Concert 1984 (Box-folder 5:25)
    - Face Dancer with Single Bullet Theory (Box-folder 5:26)
    - Faith Ringgold: Artist and Lecturer (Box-folder 5:27)
    - Film Festival (Box-folder 5:28)
    - Film-o-Rama (Box-folder 5:29)
    - Free Fall Movies for You! (Box-folder 5:30)
    - Grady Nutt: Christian Humorist and Entertainer (Box-folder 5:31)
    - Guy Van Duser and Billy Noviek Raisin' the Rent (Box-folder 5:32)
    - Hamilton Jordan (Box-folder 5:33)
    - Harry Chapin (Box-folder 5:34)
    - Heath Borthers, Jazz (Box-folder 5:35)
    - Homecoming (Box-folder 5:36)
    - Indoor Film Festival (Box-folder 5:37)
    - International Cruise 87, International Student Association & the Model United Nations Society 1987 (Box-folder 5:38)
    - Jamor (Box-folder 5:39)
    - Julian Jaynes (Box-folder 5:40)
    - Michael Manley on The 3rd World El Salvador and Jamaica (Box-folder 5:41)
    - Monarchfest Dance 1978, 2 sizes (Box-folder 5:42)
    - Monarchfest, 1st Annual -- Weekend Events, Alumni Association & Student Caucus 1978 (Box-folder 5:43)
    - Movie Poster: 3 Films 1978, 3 posters (Box-folder 5:44)
    - Night Hawks 1979 (Box-folder 5:45)
    - Night Hawks 1980 (Box-folder 5:46)
    - Openers Dance, 2 posters (Box-folder 5:47)
    - Openers Dance with Symbol 8 (Box-folder 5:48)
    - Openers Dance with the Andrew Lewis Band (Box-folder 5:49)
    - Outdoor Film Festival (Box-folder 5:50)
    - Pieces of a Dream 1984 (Box-folder 5:51)
    - Put On Your Illegal Smile -- John Prine (Box-folder 5:52)
    - Ralph Nader 1983 (Box-folder 5:53)
    - Reach for the Stars -- A Talent Show (Box-folder 5:54)
    - Sickle-cell Anemia Benefit Music Festival (Box-folder 5:55)
    - Sickle-cell Anemia Jam, A Pre-Benefit (Box-folder 5:56)
    - Skateboard Exhibition-Freestyle Contest 1977 (Box-folder 5:57)
    - Snuff and Homegrown (Box-folder 5:58)
    - Symbol 8 Big Blue Dance (Box-folder 5:59)
    - Talent Show, 2nd Annual, ODU 1977 (Box-folder 5:60)
    - Thats Not Funny, thats Sick! (Box-folder 5:61)
    - The Empire Strikes Back (Box-folder 5:62)
    - Virginia Philharmonic/ The Virginia Pops 1982-1983 (Box-folder 5:63)
    - White Water Adventure, 2 different dates (Box-folder 5:64)
  - ODU Ballet
    - Cinderella (Box-folder 5:65)
    - Come Dance with Us (Box-folder 5:66)
    - Coppe'lia (Box-folder 5:67)
    - Nutcracker, 5 different dates (Box-folder 5:68)
    - ODU Ballet: Information Poster (Box-folder 5:69)
    - Spring Concerts (Box-folder 5:70)
    - Spring Rhapsody, 3 different versions (Box-folder 5:71)
    - The Girl with Enamel Eyes (Box-folder 5:72)
    - The Israel Ballet (Box-folder 5:73)
    - The Unicorn (Box-folder 5:74)
    - Wanna Dance? (Box-folder 5:75)
  - ODU Players
    - A Flea in Her Ear (Box-folder 5:76)
    - An Enemy of the People (Box-folder 5:77)
    - Cabaret (Box-folder 5:78)
    - Canterbury Tales (Box-folder 5:79)
    - Child's Play (Box-folder 5:80)
    - Execution of Justice (Box-folder 5:81)
    - Livin' de Life (Box-folder 5:82)
    - Lysistrata (Box-folder 5:83)
    - Man of La Mancha (Box-folder 5:84)
    - Medea (Box-folder 5:85)
    - Oedipus Rex (Box-folder 5:86)
    - Pippin (Box-folder 5:87)
    - The Women (Box-folder 5:88)
  - Riverview Playhouse 1979, 1983
    - 1776 (Box-folder 5:89)
    - A Christmas Carol (Box-folder 5:90)
    - Arsenic and Old Lace by Joseph Kesselring (Box-folder 5:91)
    - Blank Poster w/ Border (Box-folder 5:92)
    - Cabaret (Box-folder 5:93)
    - Contributing to the Delinquency of an Elder by David I. Levine (Box-folder 5:94)
    - Deathtrap: A Thriller in Two Acts by Ira Levin (Box-folder 5:95)
    - Equus by Peter Shaffer (Box-folder 5:96)
    - Fifty-five Minutes from Broadway -- VA Theatre Guild (Box-folder 5:97)
    - Fifty-five Minutes from Broadway -- A Musical Revue 1983 (Box-folder 5:98)
    - George M! 1983 (Box-folder 5:99)
    - Getting Out by Marsha Norman 1983 (Box-folder 5:100)
    - Inherit the World 1983 (Box-folder 5:101)
    - John Anouilhs Antigone (Box-folder 5:102)
    - Our Town by Thornton Wilder (Box-folder 5:103)
    - Private Lives by Noel Coward (Box-folder 5:104)
    - Robber Bridegroom 1979 (Box-folder 5:105)
    - Robber Bridegroom, Cast of (Box-folder 5:106)
    - Rosencrantz and Guildenstern Are Dead (Box-folder 5:107)
    - Shenandoah (Box-folder 5:108)
    - The Importance of Being Earnest by Ernest Mauer (Box-folder 5:109)
    - The River Niger by Joseph A. Walker (Box-folder 5:110)
    - The Sea by Edward Bond (Box-folder 5:111)
    - The Three Sisters by Anton Chekhov (Box-folder 5:112)
    - Uncommon Women & Others (Box-folder 5:113)
  - University Gallery 1979
    - 2nd Annual Student Photography Exhibition (Box-folder 5:114)
    - 3rd Annual Contemporary Arts Festival (Box-folder 5:115)
    - 3rd Annual Student Photography Exhibition (Box-folder 5:116)
    - An Invitational Photography Exhibition 1979 (Box-folder 5:117)
    - Bill Taggart (Box-folder 5:118)
    - Ernest Mauer -- Linear Prevarications (Box-folder 5:119)
    - Hamrick, Benvenuto, Monk (Box-folder 5:120)
    - International Computer Art Exhibition (Box-folder 5:121)
    - Jeff Davis (Box-folder 5:122)
    - Robert Engman (Box-folder 5:123)
    - Student Art (Box-folder 5:124)
    - Student Art Exhibit (Box-folder 5:125)
    - Student Art Show (Box-folder 5:126)
    - The Old Dominion National Crafts Exhibition (Box-folder 5:127)
    - The Open Studio (Box-folder 5:128)
  - Student and Alumni Organizations 1977-1981, 1984, 1986, 1988
    - $1 Movies, Student Activities Council 1988 (Box-folder 5:129)
    - 15th Annual Student/ Businessmens Banquet, Alpha Kappa Psi Business Fraternity 1977 (Box-folder 5:130)
    - 1st Annual ODU Health Fair, ODU Student Nurses Association (Box-folder 5:131)
    - 3rd Annual Halloween Carnival, Mace & Crown 1977 (Box-folder 5:132)
    - Alumni Association -- Return to Buds Place 1986, 3 different illustrations (Box-folder 5:132)
    - Exam Jam Before You Cram (Box-folder 5:133)
    - Exercise your Right to Vote, Student Caucus (Box-folder 5:134)
    - Exercise your Right to Vote, Student Caucus (Box-folder 5:135)
    - Fun in the Sun, Student Activities/ Handicapped Student Services/ & Rec. Sports 1984 (Box-folder 5:136)
    - Gadfly, issue, 2 copies (Box-folder 5:137)
    - Gadfly, censorship, fragile (Box-folder 5:138)
    - Mark Twain on Tour, Student Activities Council (Box-folder 5:139)
    - Mark Twain on Tour, Student Activities Council (Box-folder 5:140)
    - Movie Poster The Harder they Come (Box-folder 5:141)
    - ODU Annual Student-Alumni Phonathon (Box-folder 5:142)
    - ODU Senate 1980-1981 (Box-folder 5:143)
    - Phi Mu Alpha Sinfonia Fraternity -- Sinfonia Brass Quintet (Box-folder 5:144)
    - Poetry Quartet -- Shakespeare Great Comic Series 1981 (Box-folder 5:145)
    - Stop the Spread of AIDS, AIDS Educations Committee 1988 (Box-folder 5:146)